Guide to the Burton Jesse Hendrick Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Professional Files, 1880-1963; Series II
  - Writings
    - Mellon, Andrew W. (unpublished biography)
      - Correspondence
        - General, 1938-1943 (Box 29, Folder 1)
        - A, 1940-1942 (Box 29, Folder 2)
        - Aluminum Company of America, 1940-1943 (Box 29, Folder 3)
        - Atlantic Monthly Press, 1943-1945 (Box 29, Folder 4)
        - B, 1929-1943 (Box 29, Folder 5)
        - Bruce, David, 1940-1942 (Box 29, Folder 6)
        - C, 1940-1943 (Box 29, Folder 7)
        - Carborundum Company ( E. G. Acheson), 1941 (Box 29, Folder 8)
        - D, 1940-1942 (Box 29, Folder 9)
        - E, 1943 (Box 29, Folder 10)
        - F, 1940-1943 (Box 29, Folder 11)
        - Finley, David, 1940-1943 (Box 29, Folder 12)
        - G, 1940-1942 (Box 29, Folder 13)
        - Gulf Oil Corporation, 1941-1943 (Box 29, Folder 14)
        - H, 1940-1943 (Box 29, Folder 15)
        - J, 1940-1943 (Box 30, Folder 1)
        - Koppers Company, 1941-1942 (Box 30, Folder 2)
        - L, 1940-1942 (Box 30, Folder 3)
        - M, 1940-1943 (Box 30, Folder 4)
        - McMullen, Nora (Mrs. Andrew Mellon), 1941-1942 (Box 30, Folder 5)
        - Mellon, E. P., 1940 (Box 30, Folder 6)
        - Mellon, Thomas A., 1940 (Box 30, Folder 7)
        - Mellon, William A., 1940-1943, undated (Box 30, Folder 8-10)
          Includes manuscript edits and research material.
        - N, 1941-1942 (Box 30, Folder 11)
        - P, 1940-1942 (Box 30, Folder 12)
        - Phillips, H. A., 1941-1943 (Box 30, Folder 13)
        - Reed, David A., 1942 (Box 30, Folder 14)
        - S, 1937-1943 (Box 30, Folder 15)
        - Scaife, Roger, 1940-1943 (Box 30, Folder 16)
        - T, 1940-1942 (Box 30, Folder 17)
        - U, 1940-1943 (Box 30, Folder 18)
        - W, 1940-1942 (Box 30, Folder 19)
        - Y, 1942-1943 (Box 30, Folder 20)
      - Drafts and background notes
        - Background notes, Undated (Box 31, Folder 1)
        - First draft, Circa 1940-1943
          - Chapters 1-33 (Box 31, Folder 2-8)
        - Second draft, Circa 1940-1943
          - Chapter 12 (Box 32, Folder 1)
          - Chapters 14-16 (Box 32, Folder 2-4)
          - Chapters 18-22 (Box 32, Folder 5-9)
          - Chapters 24-33 (Box 32, Folder 10-16)
        - Final draft, 1943
          - Chapters 1-10 (Box 33, Folder 1-4)
      - Research materials
        - General, 1880-circa 1942 (Box 34, Folder 1-7)
        - Subject
          - Bibliography, Circa 1940-1941 (Box 34, Folder 8)
          - Chronology, Circa 1940 (Box 34, Folder 9)
          - Donner, W. H., Union Steel, 1940 (Box 34, Folder 10)
          - Finlay, David E., 1937, 1940-1942 (Box 34, Folder 11)
          - Letterbooks
            Copies of selected pages of Andrew Mellon's correspondence.
            - Miscellaneous, 1914-1931 (Box 35, Folder 1)
            - Volumes 2-6, 1921-1924 (Box 35, Folder 2-3)
            - Volumes 10-19, 1927-1932 (Box 35, Folder 4-7)
          - Long, Gladys, 1912, 1915 (Box 35, Folder 8)
          - M. Knoedler and Company, 1899-1929 (Box 35, Folder 9)
          - Mellon, Ailsa and Paul, 1909-1929 (Box 35, Folder 10)
          - Mellon, E. P., 1908-1913 (Box 35, Folder 11)
          - Mellon, Nora McMullen, 1899-1933 (Box 35, Folder 12)
          - Mellon, Thomas, 1831-1891 (Box 36, Folder 1)
          - Mellon Brothers, 1885-1887 (Box 36, Folder 2)
          - Mellon family, 1931-1943 (Box 36, Folder 3)
          - Mellon family 1937 holdings and Hamlin diary, 1929, 1937 (Box 36, Folder 4)
          - Notes, biographical sketches, and interviews, 1940-1942 (Box 36, Folder 5-8)
          - Political, 1888-1932 (Box 36, Folder 9)
    - Page, Walter H.
      Materials for both books, Life and Letters of Walter H. Page and The Training of an American: The Earlier Life of Walter H. Page, are intermingled.
      - Correspondence
        - General, 1923-1930 (Box 37, Folder 1)
          Includes article and news clipping.
        - A, 1920-1925 (Box 37, Folder 2)
        - Alderman, Edwin A., Dr., 1920-1939 (Box 37, Folder 3)
        - Allen, James Lane, 1923 (Box 37, Folder 4)
        - American Philological Association, 1924-1926 (Box 37, Folder 5)
        - Andrews, Matthew, 1920, 1922 (Box 37, Folder 6)
        - Ashley, William, Sir, 1924 (Box 37, Folder 7)
        - Asquith, H. H., 1924 (Box 37, Folder 8)
        - Astor, Viscount and Lady, 1921 (Box 37, Folder 9)
        - B, 1920-1930 (Box 37, Folder 10)
        - Badè, William Frederic, Professor, 1920-1921 (Box 37, Folder 11)
        - Bailey, Liberty H., 1920-1925 (Box 37, Folder 12)
        - Baker, Newton D., 1922 (Box 37, Folder 13)
        - Baker, Ray S., 1920-1927 (Box 37, Folder 14)
        - Baldwin, William E., 1923 (Box 37, Folder 15)
        - Barnard, George Grey, 1920-1925 (Box 37, Folder 16)
        - Barran, John, Sir, 1924 (Box 37, Folder 17)
        - Barratt, J. Arthur, 1924 (Box 37, Folder 18)
        - Barton, Bruce, 1922, 1937 (Box 37, Folder 19)
        - Baruch, Bernard M., 1923 (Box 37, Folder 20)
        - Bassett, John S., 1920-1925 (Box 37, Folder 21)
        - Battle, George Gordon, 1920-1924 (Box 37, Folder 22)
        - Bax, Emily, 1924-1930 (Box 37, Folder 23)
        - Beach, Charles F., 1922 (Box 37, Folder 24)
        - Beit, Otto, Sir, 1924 (Box 37, Folder 25)
        - Bell, Edward Price, 1924 (Box 37, Folder 26)
        - Bennett, F. M., Captain, 1923 (Box 37, Folder 27)
        - Bingham School, 1923, 1926 (Box 37, Folder 28)
        - Bishop, George R., 1922-1925 (Box 37, Folder 29)
        - Bishop, Joseph B., 1920 (Box 37, Folder 30)
        - Blackwell, Robert B., Dr., 1920-1927 (Box 37, Folder 31)
        - Blair, William A., 1920, 1925 (Box 37, Folder 32)
        - Blethen, Joseph, 1920 (Box 37, Folder 33)
        - Bok, Edward W., 1923-1924 (Box 37, Folder 34)
        - Bourland, A. P., 1924-1927 (Box 37, Folder 35)
        - Boyd, William K., Dr., 1923-1927 (Box 37, Folder 36)
        - Boyle, Virginia Frazer, 1925 (Box 37, Folder 37)
        - Branson, E. C., Dr., 1920-1924 (Box 37, Folder 38)
        - Brent, Charles H., Bishop, 1924 (Box 37, Folder 39)
        - Brittain, Harry, Sir, 1924 (Box 37, Folder 40)
        - Brooks, John Graham, 1901, 1924 (Box 37, Folder 41)
          Includes copy of 1901 Dec 18 letter from Page.
        - Broughton, Carrie L., North Carolina State Library, 1924 (Box 37, Folder 42)
        - Brown, Joseph, 1923-1924 (Box 37, Folder 43)
        - Brownrigg, Douglas, Rear Admiral Sir, 1918-1924 (Box 37, Folder 44)
        - Bruce, William Cabell, 1925 (Box 37, Folder 45)
        - Bryce, E. Marion, Viscountess, 1923-1924 (Box 37, Folder 46)
        - Buckler, William H., 1920-1921 (Box 37, Folder 47)
        - Burghclere, Lady, 1924 (Box 37, Folder 48)
        - Burne-Jones, Philip, Sir, 1924 (Box 37, Folder 49)
        - Butterfield, Kenyon, Dr., 1920-1925 (Box 37, Folder 50)
        - Buttrick, Wallace, Dr., 1919-1925 (Box 37, Folder 51)
        - C, 1920-1940 (Box 38, Folder 1)
        - Chamberlain, Austen, 1924 (Box 38, Folder 2)
        - Chamberlain, J. R., Mrs. (G. Hope Summerell), 1926 (Box 38, Folder 3)
          Correspondence concerning History of Wake County.
        - Chambers, D. L., 1925 (Box 38, Folder 4)
        - Chapman, Frank M., 1920, 1925 (Box 38, Folder 5)
        - Chapman, John Jay, 1923 (Box 38, Folder 6)
        - Clark, Kate Upson, 1925 (Box 38, Folder 7)
        - Claxton, Philander P., Dr., 1920-1922 (Box 38, Folder 8)
        - Clifford, Inez (Mrs. W. K.), 1924 (Box 38, Folder 9)
        - Connor, R. D. W., 1923-1924 (Box 38, Folder 10)
        - Cook, Albert S., 1924 (Box 38, Folder 11)
        - Cooper, W. A., Reverend, 1924-1926 (Box 38, Folder 12)
        - Copeland, Charles T., 1923-1924 (Box 38, Folder 13)
        - Cortissoz, Royal, 1920 (Box 38, Folder 14)
        - Cowdray, Lord, 1924 (Box 38, Folder 15)
        - Cramton, Louis, 1944 (Box 38, Folder 16)
        - Cranage, D. H. S., Reverend, 1924 (Box 38, Folder 17)
        - Cushing, Harvey, 1923 (Box 38, Folder 18)
        - D, 1920-1926 (Box 38, Folder 19)
        - Dabney, Charles W., 1920-1932 (Box 38, Folder 20)
        - Dafoe, J. W., 1924 (Box 38, Folder 21)
        - Dawson, Geoffrey, The Times (London), 1924 (Box 38, Folder 22)
        - De Kalb, Courtney, 1920 (Box 38, Folder 23)
        - Dent, J. M., 1924 (Box 38, Folder 24)
        - Dickerman, G. S., Reverend, 1925-1927 (Box 38, Folder 25)
        - Dickson, Frederick S., 1923 (Box 38, Folder 26)
        - Dickson, Harris, 1920-1922 (Box 38, Folder 27)
        - Dillard, James H., 1920-1927 (Box 38, Folder 28)
        - Dixon, Thomas, 1920-1925 (Box 38, Folder 29)
        - Dominguez, Madame de, 1926 (Box 38, Folder 30)
        - Doubleday, Frank Nelson, 1920-1928 (Box 38, Folder 31)
        - Dreher, Julius, 1923-1927 (Box 38, Folder 32)
        - Dreher, William, 1923-1928 (Box 38, Folder 33)
        - Dunn, Arthur, 1920 (Box 38, Folder 34)
        - E, 1922-1926 (Box 38, Folder 35)
        - Edmonds, Richard, 1924 (Box 38, Folder 36)
        - Eliot, Charles W., Dr., 1925-1927 (Box 38, Folder 37)
        - Encyclopedia Britannica, 1926-1929 (Box 38, Folder 38)
        - F, 1921-1927 (Box 38, Folder 39)
        - Few, W. P., 1929-1932 (Box 38, Folder 40)
        - Fisher, Irving, 1920-1922 (Box 38, Folder 41)
        - Fitzhugh, W. H., 1923 (Box 38, Folder 42)
        - Flexner, Abraham, 1920-1928 (Box 38, Folder 43)
        - Fowler, Harold, 1925, 1935 (Box 38, Folder 44)
        - Fries, Henry E., 1920-1922 (Box 38, Folder 45)
        - Frost, William G., 1920 (Box 38, Folder 46)
        - Fuller, W. W., 1920-1924 (Box 38, Folder 47)
        - G, 1920-1926 (Box 38, Folder 48)
        - Garland, Hamlin, 1923-1925 (Box 38, Folder 49)
        - Garvin, J. L., 1924-1929 (Box 38, Folder 50)
        - Gilman, Elizabeth, 1927-1928 (Box 38, Folder 51)
        - Gilmer, Oswald M., Judge, 1923 (Box 38, Folder 52)
        - Goode, William, Sir, 1924 (Box 38, Folder 53)
        - Goodrich, Arthur, 1923-1925 (Box 38, Folder 54)
        - Grammer, Carl E., 1925 (Box 38, Folder 55)
        - Graves, Mildred (Mrs. Louis), 1926 (Box 38, Folder 56)
        - Greenslet, Ferris, 1925 (Box 38, Folder 57)
        - Gregg, James E., 1927 (Box 38, Folder 58)
        - Grey of Fallodon, Viscount, 1921-1926 (Box 38, Folder 59)
        - Grubb, Eugene H., 1920 (Box 38, Folder 60)
        - H, 1920-1926 (Box 39, Folder 1)
        - Hadfield, Robert, Sir, 1924 (Box 39, Folder 2)
        - Hall, Reginald, Admiral Sir, 1921-1928 (Box 39, Folder 3)
        - Hamilton, George, Lord, 1924 (Box 39, Folder 4)
        - Hanks, Sarah E. Jasper, 1920-1928 (Box 39, Folder 5)
        - Hanus, Paul H., 1925 (Box 39, Folder 6)
        - Harris, Cary Page (Mrs. Fletcher), 1926 (Box 39, Folder 7)
        - Harris, Julia Collier and Esther LaRose (Mrs. Joel Chandler), 1920-1927 (Box 39, Folder 8)
        - Herron, Emily K., 1920-1932 (Box 39, Folder 9)
        - Hibben, John Grier, 1925 (Box 39, Folder 10)
        - Hill, John Sprunt, 1924 (Box 39, Folder 11)
        - Hodges, J. D., 1928 (Box 39, Folder 12)
        - Houghton Mifflin Company, 1927-1928 (Box 39, Folder 13)
        - House, Edward M., 1920-1927 (Box 39, Folder 14)
        - Houston, Mrs. C. F., 1927 (Box 39, Folder 15)
        - Houston, David F., 1920-1925 (Box 39, Folder 16)
        - Howe, M. A. De Wolfe, 1923 (Box 39, Folder 17)
        - Howland, Louis, 1920-1924 (Box 39, Folder 18)
        - Hudson, Robert, Sir, 1924 (Box 39, Folder 19)
        - J, 1920-1925 (Box 39, Folder 20)
        - Jacques, William W., 1923 (Box 39, Folder 21)
          Includes manuscript of Jacques' recollections of Page.
        - Jenkins, McGregor, 1924-1926 (Box 39, Folder 22)
        - Johnson, Mary, 1920-1922 (Box 39, Folder 23)
        - Johnson, Robert Underwood, 1927-1932 (Box 39, Folder 24)
        - Jones, Henry Arthur, 1924 (Box 39, Folder 25)
        - Joyner, James Y., 1920-1923 (Box 39, Folder 26)
        - K, 1921-1931 (Box 39, Folder 27)
        - Kaneko, Kentaro, Baron, 1920-1925 (Box 39, Folder 28)
        - Kaufman, Nathan, 1926-1928 (Box 39, Folder 29)
        - Keen, W. W., 1923-1925 (Box 39, Folder 30)
        - Keet, Alfred E., 1922 (Box 39, Folder 31)
        - Kellogg, Frank B., 1925 (Box 39, Folder 32)
        - Kerr, Philip, 1924 (Box 39, Folder 33)
        - Keys, C. M., 1920-1925 (Box 39, Folder 34)
        - Kirkland, J. H., 1920-1924 (Box 39, Folder 35)
        - L, 1920-1924 (Box 40, Folder 1)
        - Lanier, Henry, 1924 (Box 40, Folder 2)
        - Lansing, Robert, 1920 (Box 40, Folder 3)
        - Laughlin, Irwin, 1920-1927 (Box 40, Folder 4)
        - Lawrence, Walter Roper, Sir, 1924 (Box 40, Folder 5)
        - Leach, Henry, 1924 (Box 40, Folder 6)
        - Library of Congress, 1924-1926 (Box 40, Folder 7)
        - Lodge, Henry Cabot, 1929 (Box 40, Folder 8)
        - Long, Arthur W., 1924 (Box 40, Folder 9)
        - Long, B. F., Judge, 1922-1925 (Box 40, Folder 10)
        - Loring, Charles, 1920-1930 (Box 40, Folder 11)
        - M, 1923-1925 (Box 40, Folder 12)
        - MacAlister, Donald, Sir, 1924 (Box 40, Folder 13)
        - Martin, O. B., 1920 (Box 40, Folder 14)
        - McAdoo, William, 1911, 1920-1921 (Box 40, Folder 15)
        - McAndrew, William, 1919-1924 (Box 40, Folder 16)
        - McCarthy, Charles, 1920 (Box 40, Folder 17)
        - McCorkle, Walter L., 1924-1925 (Box 40, Folder 18)
        - McIver, Charles, 1920-1926 (Box 40, Folder 19)
        - McKelway, Virginia Brooks (Mrs. St. Clair), 1920 (Box 40, Folder 20)
          Includes copies of 1908-1909 correspondence with Page.
        - McNeill, Martha Chamberlayne (Mrs. Walter), 1926 (Box 40, Folder 21)
        - McRae, Hugh, 1920, 1925 (Box 40, Folder 22)
        - Mifflin, G. H., 1920 (Box 40, Folder 23)
        - Miller, C. W. E., 1927-1928 (Box 40, Folder 24)
        - Mims, Edwin, 1919-1926 (Box 40, Folder 25)
        - Mitchell, Samuel C., 1920-1926 (Box 40, Folder 26)
        - Montagne, Andrew J., 1923-1925 (Box 40, Folder 27)
        - Moore, Charles, 1923-1926 (Box 40, Folder 28)
        - Moore, John Bassett, 1920 (Box 40, Folder 29)
        - Morgenthau, Henry, 1920 (Box 40, Folder 30)
        - N, 1923-1925 (Box 40, Folder 31)
        - Nelson, Nelson O., 1920 (Box 40, Folder 32)
        - Nesbitt, Charles, Dr., 1920-1923 (Box 40, Folder 33)
        - Nicholson, Meredith, 1920-1923 (Box 40, Folder 34)
        - O, 1920-1923 (Box 41, Folder 1)
        - Oldham, Edward A., 1920-1926 (Box 41, Folder 2)
        - P, 1920-1925 (Box 41, Folder 3)
        - Page, Alice W. (Mrs. Walter E.), 1921-1927 (Box 41, Folder 4)
        - Page, Arthur W., 1918-1932 (Box 41, Folder 5)
        - Page, Frank, 1925 (Box 41, Folder 6)
        - Page, Henry, 1922 (Box 41, Folder 7)
        - Page, Mary, 1920 (Box 41, Folder 8)
        - Page, Robert, 1920-1922 (Box 41, Folder 9)
        - Page, Rosewell, 1924 (Box 41, Folder 10)
        - Paine, Henry G., 1923-1926 (Box 41, Folder 11)
          Copy of interview transcript included.
        - Parker, George F., 1923-1924 (Box 41, Folder 12)
        - Parker, Gilbert, Sir, 1924-1927 (Box 41, Folder 13)
          Includes copy of 1918 Page letter.
        - Parker, Hayward, 1926 (Box 41, Folder 14)
        - Parks, M. M., 1920-1926 (Box 41, Folder 15)
        - Payne, Bruce R., 1922-1925 (Box 41, Folder 16)
        - Pemberton, Virginia Carroll ((Mrs. W. H.), 1920, 1926 (Box 41, Folder 17)
        - Pennell, Elizabeth Robins (Mrs. Joseph), 1927 (Box 41, Folder 18)
        - Pennoyer, Richard F., 1921 (Box 41, Folder 19)
        - Perry, Bliss, 1923-1924 (Box 41, Folder 20)
        - Phelps, William Lyon, 1923-1928 (Box 41, Folder 21)
        - Phillips, William, 1920 (Box 41, Folder 22)
        - Pinchot, Gifford, 1920-1923 (Box 41, Folder 23)
        - Plimpton, George A., 1924, 1927 (Box 41, Folder 24)
        - Plunkett, Horace, Sir, 1920-1924 (Box 41, Folder 25)
        - Polk, Frank L., 1920-1922 (Box 41, Folder 26)
        - Presbrey, Frank, 1920-1924 (Box 41, Folder 27)
        - Price, Theodore H. and Thomas, 1923-1928 (Box 41, Folder 28)
        - Primrose, John S., 1920 (Box 41, Folder 29)
        - Pritchett, Henry S., 1920 (Box 41, Folder 30)
        - R, 1923-1926 (Box 41, Folder 31)
        - Rallisford, N. J., 1923 (Box 41, Folder 32)
        - Rayleigh, Dowager Lady, 1924 (Box 41, Folder 33)
        - Rice, Kale Y., 1924 (Box 41, Folder 34)
        - Roberts, Chalmers, 1924 (Box 41, Folder 35)
          Correspondence regarding Admiral Reginald Hall.
        - Robins, Sally N., 1924 (Box 41, Folder 36)
        - Rose, Wickliffe, 1920-1922 (Box 41, Folder 37)
        - Russell, Lindsay, 1920 (Box 41, Folder 38)
        - S, 1920-1927 (Box 41, Folder 39)
        - Sandwich, Lord, 1924 (Box 41, Folder 40)
        - Scaife, Roger, 1923-1927 (Box 41, Folder 41)
          Concerning Page letters to Professor Bliss Parry.
        - Scott, Leroy, 1924 (Box 41, Folder 42)
        - Scudder, Winthrop and Horace, 1922, 1925 (Box 41, Folder 43)
        - See, T. T. J., Dr., 1920-1922 (Box 41, Folder 44)
        - Seitz, Don C., 1924-1925 (Box 41, Folder 45)
        - Selbourne, Earl of, 1924 (Box 41, Folder 46)
        - Sherwood, Renaud, 1925-1926 (Box 41, Folder 47)
        - Shipley, Arthur, Sir, 1924 (Box 41, Folder 48)
        - Shipp, Thomas, 1920 (Box 41, Folder 49)
        - Shoecraft, Eugene, 1918-1928 (Box 41, Folder 50)
        - Smith, C. Alphonso, 1920-1924 (Box 41, Folder 51)
        - Smith, M. A., Mrs., 1926, 1928 (Box 41, Folder 52)
        - Solley, John B., Jr., 1924 (Box 41, Folder 53)
        - Speyer, James, 1922-1925 (Box 41, Folder 54)
        - Squier, George O., General, 1925 (Box 41, Folder 55)
        - State Department, U. S., 1925 (Box 41, Folder 56)
        - Stiles, Charles W., 1920-1922 (Box 41, Folder 57)
        - Stokes, Anson Phelps, Reverend, 1923 (Box 41, Folder 58)
        - Stokes, Frederick A., 1925 (Box 41, Folder 59)
        - Sturges, Hollister, 1926-1928 (Box 41, Folder 60)
        - Sydenham of Combe, Lord, 1924 (Box 41, Folder 61)
        - Symington, Powers, 1924-1925 (Box 41, Folder 62)
        - T, 1922-1928 (Box 42, Folder 1)
        - Templeton, J. M., Jr., 1926-1932 (Box 42, Folder 2)
        - Thayer, William Roscoe, 1921-1925 (Box 42, Folder 3)
        - Thomson, Basil, Sir, 1921 (Box 42, Folder 4)
        - Thornton, Mary, 1920-1928 (Box 42, Folder 5)
        - Thwing, Charles F., 1923-1925 (Box 42, Folder 6)
        - Tillett, Charles and Wilbur, 1920-1927 (Box 42, Folder 7)
        - Trinity College, 1922-1923 (Box 42, Folder 8)
          Includes many reminiscences and letters of Trinity men.
        - Turner, Frederick, Professor, 1924 (Box 42, Folder 9)
        - Turner, Raymond, Professor, Johns Hopkins University, 1927 (Box 42, Folder 10)
        - Tuskegee Institute, 1920-1927 (Box 42, Folder 11)
        - Tyrrell, William, Sir, 1921-1925 (Box 42, Folder 12)
        - Villard, Oswald Garrison, 1925-1926 (Box 42, Folder 13)
        - W, 1920-1930 (Box 42, Folder 14)
        - Wade, John, Professor, 1924 (Box 42, Folder 15)
        - Wainwright, Julia Foraker, 1925 (Box 42, Folder 16)
        - Wallace, Henry, 1920-1923 (Box 42, Folder 17)
        - Walston, Charles, Sir, 1918-1926 (Box 42, Folder 18)
          Includes news clippings and Page letter.
        - Wardlow, Albert G., Reverend, 1923-1928 (Box 42, Folder 19)
        - White, Henry, 1920-1927 (Box 42, Folder 20)
        - White, W. A., 1920 (Box 42, Folder 21)
        - Winston, George, Professor, 1920-1926 (Box 42, Folder 22)
        - Winston, Robert W., 1922 (Box 42, Folder 23)
        - Wood, Leonard, General, 1920-1922 (Box 42, Folder 24)
        - Wright, J. Butler, 1925 (Box 42, Folder 25)
        - York, Archbishop of, 1924 (Box 42, Folder 26)
        - Zimmermann chapter, 1925-1927 (Box 42, Folder 27)
      - Research material, 1916-1928 (Box 42, Folder 28-29)
    - "Polygamy in Mexico" (article)
      - Research notes and news clippings, 1910 (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - "Pork Barrel Pensions"
      - Correspondence -- Pritchett, Henry, 1908 (Box 43, Folder 2)
      - Publication -- "Pork Barrel Pensions: A Scandal in Which Both Political Parties Strive to Excel", 1915 (Box 43, Folder 3)
        Reprinted from the World's Work.
    - Statesmen of the Lost Cause: Jefferson Davis and His Cabinet
      - Correspondence, 1936-1946 (Box 43, Folder 4)
      - News clippings, 1939-1940 (Box 43, Folder 5-6)
      - Notes, Undated (Box 43, Folder 7)
      - Portraits, Undated (Box 43, Folder 8)
        Includes a few images of buildings.
    - "The Story of Life Insurance"
      - Correspondence and news clippings, 1906, 1930 (Box 43, Folder 9)
      - Sullivan, Mark -- correspondence, 1927-1930 (Box 43, Folder 10)
        Includes material on Carnegie research.
    - Victory at Sea
      - Correspondence
        - Brewerton, Dorothy, 1940 (Box 44, Folder 1)
        - Sims, William S., Admiral, 1917-1928 (Box 44, Folder 2)
      - News clippings and reviews, 1920 (Box 44, Folder 3)